Anko! Oh, my gosh!
Wow!
That's a great visual.
I'm feeling like I'm a fan of anbuta (red bean paste)
I'm feeling it at a great speed now!
Hi, I'm Mizuki Hiraoka from Hinatazaka46. I'm Mitsuki Hiraoka from Hyugaizaka46.
Today, I'm here in Nagoya.
Yay!
What did I come here for?
I really love anko (red bean paste),
I love anko so much that I cook it myself,
I love anko so much that I cook it myself.
I, Mizuki Hiraoka, who loves anko so much, have researched the best 3 best anko butters in Nagoya.
I, Mizuki Hiraoka, who loves anko (red bean paste) so much, researched the best 3 best anko butters
I would like to go around Nagoya.
I am looking forward to it.
I would like to go to the first store right away.
Yes, about my relationship with anko,
Well, if someone were to ask me what kind of relationship I have with Anko,
I would be a little bit hesitant to answer.
How did you come to like Anko?
I have always liked Japanese sweets very much,
My favorite Japanese sweets were dorayaki and taiyaki,
monaka, and so on.
I thought, "They all contain anko (red bean paste),
That's when I realized that I like anko (red bean paste).
I realized that I like anko.
The place I am going to now,
Rose Coffee,It's called Rose Coffee,
It's a very nice and stylish cafe,
In terms of style,
It's a very traditional style, with butter on top of red bean paste,
The style of the butter was very innovative,
The style of the butter is very innovative,
I'm really looking forward to it.
After chatting with them, they arrived,
It's here.
Ta-da! It looks like this. A very nice cafe.
I'd like to go in immediately.
Hello. I am looking forward to working with you.
Then, I would like to order right away.
I would like to order the famous homemade unbuttered toast.
Please order it.
Do you have any specialties?
When you say "specially made", do you mean the anko is specially made or the butter? Is the butter special?
The anko is homemade.
Oh, I see.
It's homemade, so we're making it today.
That's great. I sometimes make it at home too.
It's a great bread. I like it too.
I love it.
You can see it from here.
You can smell the bread. The aroma of savory bread. I'm looking forward to it.
Here they come! Thank you very much. Bon appétit.
Wow, this is amazing. Looks delicious.
It's our special unbuttered toast.
Look at this. Look at this butter. Isn't it amazing?Look at this. Look at this butter. Isn't it amazing?
It's not easy to find. The way this butter rides.
It's an art.
I'd like to try it right away.
It's my beloved unbuttered butter.
I'm thrilled.
It's delicious.
Ah...
Mm...
It's so delicious.
What can I say?
It has a salty buttery taste.
And the red bean paste has a hint of the skin.
I love tsubu-an.
I love tsubu-an (bean jam), but most of them are too soft and crunchy
I love tsubu-an, but most of them are too soft and crunchy.
But this bean jam is quite fresh.
It's a very moist bean jam.
And yet it still has a hint of the skin.
It's really rare.
It's really delicious.
Delicious!
It's so good!
The butter is melting and it's creamier than before.
Butter and red bean paste are now in excellent proportions.
Bizuki no Kannai is
Delicious!
Delicious!Delicious!
Delicious
Bizuki no Kannai wa
It's a festival!
I'm feeling that I love unbuttered food.
I'm feeling it at a great speed now!
Thank you for the food!
I finished it!
It was delicious!
Next, I would like to go to the second store!
The second store is, let's see... Takehisa Coffee!
There are two kinds of breads to choose from: regular toast and a round bread called Kaiser toast!
I'm really interested in the Kaiser toast!
I've seen the visual of the Kaiser toast with a lot of red bean paste on it.
It's so famous that I'm sure everyone who loves red bean paste knows about it.
I've been wanting to go there for a long time!
So I'm really looking forward to it, and I'm really excited about it!
We found it!
We've arrived at Manager's Coffee!
Let's go in!
We've arrived!
Are you sure you want to order? Yes, I'm fine.
One half of a piece of Ogla toast with Kaiser toast.
Is that okay? Yes, that's fine.
This is how it's all about the bean paste.
I'm just showing you this.
It's very special.Something really special.
Full of nutrients and amazing!
It's a product that is packed full of
I can see why you are so particular about this product.
Thank you very much!
It's amazing!
Ta-da! Looks delicious!
The texture of this mountain is wonderful!
The texture of the bean paste is like this
I'm eating it.
You can see these grains are still there, right?
These grains are still there!
Bon appétit!
εια petrol
Mmmm! It's so azuki! Amazing!
I'm so impressed!
The taste of the azuki beans themselves is really alive.
The sweetness is really low.
But the sweetness of this bread and the sweetness of this azuki
The sweetness that this azuki bean has by nature is enhanced.
This is the first red bean paste I've ever had. Really. Amazing!
The bread was also made with Kaiser toast, which is a round type of bread.
It's very sticky and delicious. Amazing!
The bread is buttered.
The more you chew, the more butter you feel!
Really, you could probably eat a whole lot of this anko!
I'd like to try just a little bit of the red bean paste!
I'd like to try just the bean jam!
I'd like to try just the red bean paste!
Mmm~~M~~~
The azuki beans are still there, still blanched and not crushed.
and the dried bean jam
It's a nice mix of the two.
The red bean paste is just like a sweet bean paste, and each of them asserts itself in your mouth.
The fresh cream is not too sweet.
The soft-serve ice cream has a very strong soft-serve ice cream milk taste.
I love the combination of whipped cream and red bean paste.
It's a definite combination, really!
It was really delicious.
Thank you very much.
May I have one of your stickers?
Yes!
I got a sticker.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the food.
I found something here
I found something that caught my attention.
I went downstairs.
Ta-da!
Can you see it? This is it, ladies and gentlemen.
Here it is.
Nagoya Castle.
Yes!
And here, at the top...
The famous
That's her.
It's Shachihoko.
How was the ride with Shachihoko? It's something like this...How was it riding on Sha Chihoko? It's something like this.
I'm here to see you.
Haruharu Haruharu!
I'm in front of Shachihoko!
You came to see me on this, Haruharu?
Yes, we're close by!
The next store is...
Tsubame Bakery!
This store is...
The ingredients of the bread and the sweet bean paste...
They seem to be a bakery that is particular about their ingredients.
I'm really looking forward to it!
On my days off, I go to various bakeries in Tokyo
I collect unbuttoned sandwiches and so on.
I eat a little bit at a time.
So you really like going to bakeries and looking for anko (red bean paste).
I also like going to bakeries and looking for anko (red bean paste).
I can see it now!
Tsubame Pan
Well, I'd like to get started.
Here we go.
Good afternoon.
I'd like to go to my seat.
It smells like bread.
It's so natural.
It's like we're outside.
Excuse me.
Ogla toast, please.
We're very particular about our ogla toast.
We use ogla from Iseya.We use ogla from Iseseia
The cream and pasta are made in Hokkaido
The wheat used for the bread itself is also from Hokkaido!
It's just like Hokkaido!
I'm looking forward to it!
I can't wait to see how they make their bread!
I'll film you making it.
May I see what you're doing?
Of course.
The bread is coming out.
Anko!
It's amazing!
Anko from Iseya.
It's on the top!
Plenty of it!
Finally, put butter on it!
It's done!
Thank you so much!
It looks amazing!
It's a great visual.
Thank you very much.
Here it is!
Looks delicious.
Wow, that's nice.
Bon appétit!
Another new
The appeal of anko (red bean paste)
The appeal of anko (red bean paste) is being promoted!
My first impression is that it might be a little bit western style
I knew it would be the creaminess of this cream andThe creaminess of the cream and the sweetness of the bread
The sweetness of the bread is mild and gentle.
Anyway, when you want to eat something sweet with a lot of sugar
Anyway, when I want to eat something sweet with a lot of sugar
When I want to eat something sweet and filling, this oeuvre toast is just what I need.
Oeuvre toast.
Thank you for watching to the end.
See you next time with a delicious video.
Bye.
Azurim are hot cola not much flu physically!
Thanks for the food.
I finished the meal.
I was impressed with the first bite.
Until the last bite.
I could taste it.
It was very delicious.
Thank you for the meal.
Today, Mizuki Hiraoka researched
Nagoya's ogla toast
The best 3
I went there,
It was really worth the research.
It was worth the effort to come all the way here.
It was delicious all the way and I was happy all the way,
really.
I really wanted to stay in Nagoya
I wanted to stay in Nagoya all the time.
I will never let my love for anko
I will continue to nurture my love for Anko.I will try to nurture it.
Thank you for watching today.
Good button and subscribe to our channel.
and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.